In this brief video we're going to talk about alignment. A very low level but very
在这段简短的视频中，我们将讨论对齐。非常低的水平，但是非常低
important detail of machine architecture that every compiler writer needs to be
每个编译器编写者都需要具备的机器体系结构的重要细节
aware of. First, let's review a few properties of Contemporary machines.
意识到了。首先，让我们回顾一下当代机器的一些特性。
Currently, most modern machines are either 32 or 64 bit meaning you have the 32 or 64
目前，大多数现代计算机不是32位就是64位，这意味着您可以使用32位或64位
bits in a word and the word is actually subdivided into smaller units. We would
字中的比特和该字实际上被细分为更小的单元。我们会
say that there are eight bits in a bye and then four or eight byes in word depending
假设在BYE中有8位，然后在字中有4或8个BYE，视情况而定
whether it's a 32 or 64 bit machine. And other important property is that machines
无论是32位机器还是64位机器。其他重要的属性是机器
can be either byte or word addressable. Meaning that in the native language of the
可以是字节或字可寻址的。也就是说，在他们的母语中
machine in machine code it may be possible to either name only entire words or it may
机器代码中的机器，可以只命名整个单词，也可以
be possible to reference memory at the granule area of individual bytes. They say
可以在单个字节的区块区域引用内存。他们说
that data is word aligned if it begins at a word boundary. So if we think about.
如果该数据开始于字边界，则该数据是字对齐的。所以如果我们想一想。
Data in memory or the organization in the memory and is laid out into bytes. And
存储器中的数据或存储器中的组织，并以字节为单位进行布局。和
let's say. That this is a 32-bit machines so that four bytes make a word and one
比方说。这是一台32位的机器，所以四个字节就是一个字加一个字
word begins here and the next word begins here and if data is allocated on a word
字从这里开始，下一个字从这里开始，如果在一个字上分配了数据
boundary, say, it needs more bytes then that would be a word a line a piece of
边界，比方说，它需要更多的字节，而不是一个字、一行、一段
data. If a piece of data begins in the middle of the word, so let's say for
数据。如果一段数据开始于单词的中间，那么让我们假设
example that begins here, and we have some data that's allocated here, this data is
从这里开始的示例，我们在这里分配了一些数据，这些数据是
not word aligned, doesn't begin on a word boundary And the important property or the
不是单词对齐，不是从单词边界开始，并且重要属性或
important issue is that most machines have some alignment restrictions. So these
重要的问题是，大多数机器都有一些对齐限制。所以这些都是
restrictions come in one of two forms. So, on some machines, if the data is not
限制有两种形式之一。因此，在某些机器上，如果数据不是
properly aligned, meaning that you tried to reference data that isn't aligned the
正确对齐，这意味着您试图引用未对齐的数据
way the machines requires, then the machine may just fail to execute that
机器需要的方式，那么机器可能就不能执行该操作
instruction. Your program may hang or even the machine may hang and it's, but, the
指示。您的程序可能会挂起，甚至机器可能会挂起，但是
important thing is that program will not execute correctly. So there's a, it's
重要的是程序不会正确执行。所以有一个，它是
incorrect to not have the data aligned properly. Now, there are other machines
没有正确对齐数据是不正确的。现在，还有其他的机器
that well, actually al low you to put the data anywhere you like but at a
那好，实际上允许你把数据放在你喜欢的任何地方，但不是放在
significantly cause And maybe that accessing data that is aligned in word
可能会导致访问Word中对齐数据
boundaries is cheaper than accessing that's on non-word boundaries And these
边界比访问非单词边界上的边界更便宜，这些
performance penalties Are often dramatic so it can easily be ten times lower to
性能损失通常是戏剧性的，因此可以很容易地将其降低到
access missile line data than to access data that has the alignment favored by
访问导弹线路数据，而不是访问具有以下有利对齐方式的数据
that particular machine. So let's take a look at an example where data alignment
那台特殊的机器。那么让我们来看一个数据对齐的示例
issue tend to come up. One of the most common situations where we have to worry
问题往往会浮出水面。我们必须担心的最常见的情况之一
about the alignment is in the allocation of strings. So let's say we have this
关于对齐是在字符串的分配上。所以让我们假设我们有这个
string, the string Hello and then we want to put it in memory. So let me draw our
字符串，字符串Hello，然后我们想把它放到内存中。所以让我把我们的
memory as a linear sequence of bytes so I'll mark out some bytes here. And let's
内存是一个线性字节序列，所以我在这里标出一些字节。让我们
assume this is a 32-bit machine so let me make the word boundaries a little bit
假设这是一台32位的机器，那么让我稍微定义一下字边界
heavier boundaries. So, one, two, three, four. Okay. So, there are the, the word
更重的界限。所以，一，二，三，四。好吧。所以，有这个，这个词
boundaries And now let's say there were we are trying to have aligned data, a word
边界，现在假设我们正在尝试将数据对齐，一个词
aligned data and so allocate this string beginning in the word boundary. So, the
对齐的数据，因此从单词边界开始分配此字符串。所以呢，这个
each character will go on the first byte when e, then l, then l, then o. And now,
当e，然后l，然后l，然后o时，每个字符将在第一个字节上。现在，
we may have terminating null depending on how strings are implemented. And let's
根据字符串的实现方式，我们可能会有终止NULL。让我们
assume that we do. And this is fine placement of the strings extremely begins
假设我们是这样做的。这是非常好的琴弦摆放方式
in the word boundary and. That assess by presumably any alignment restrictions of
在“边界和”这个词中。它大概通过任何对齐限制来评估
the machine and now the question is where does the next data item go? So we could
现在的问题是下一个数据项要到哪里去？这样我们就可以
begin the next data item right in the next available byte and that would be good if
从下一个可用字节开始下一个数据项，如果
we are very concerned about not wasting memory. But, I noticed that, that data
我们非常关心不浪费内存。但是，我注意到，那些数据
item will then be were aligned. We may either run into correctness or performance
然后项目将被对齐。我们可能会遇到正确的问题，也可能会遇到性能问题。
problems if the machine has restrictions on the alignment. So, the simple solution
如果机器对齐有限制，则会出现问题。所以，简单的解决方案
here is to simply skip to the next word boundary and allocate the next data item
这里只需跳到下一个词边界并分配下一个数据项
whenever it is on the next word beginning at the next word boundary. And what
只要它在从下一个词边界开始的下一个词上。还有什么
happens to this two bytes here, well these bytes are just junks. T hey're not used at
发生在这两个字节上，好吧，这些字节都是垃圾。它不是用在
all, they never reference by the program. It doesn't matter what they're value is
所有的，他们从来没有被程序引用过。它们的价值是什么并不重要
because the program should never refer to them. It's just unused memory. And note
因为程序永远不应该引用它们。这只是未使用的内存。并请注意
that if we didn't have the terminating zero then there would be the terminating,
如果我们没有终止零点，那么就会有终止点，
no character then and then would be three unused bytes after the string. So to
那么没有字符，那么字符串之后将是三个未使用的字节。所以要
summarize this is the general strategy for dealing with alignment when you have
总结一下，这是在以下情况下处理对齐的一般策略
alignment restrictions. Data begins on the boundaries, typically word boundaries that
对齐限制。数据开始于边界，通常是
are required and if the particular data that you're allocating has a none integral
是必需的，并且如果要分配的特定数据具有非整数
length. Meaning that it doesn't end directly on the next required boundary and
长度。这意味着它不会直接结束在下一个所需的边界上，并且
you just skip over whenever bytes are in between to get the data, the next data
您只需跳过介于两个字节之间的任何时间来获取数据，即下一个数据
that's going to be allocated on the correct boundary.
这将被分配到正确的边界上。